We'll call it over theime especially
you feel that door for me.
Monday, March 4th, May 4th.
Again, the room is getting personal experiences.
Hi, I'm Liz.
I'm Ruth.
She said the door for Williams,
Denver, Parker.
Hi.
Six minutes from the door for you to 20,
every 20, 20, 24, or whatever.
The door for Williams,
he said Parker.
Hi.
Seven days right from many clients,
spent at college.
He already had a relationship in such a good place.
For a season, about 24, 818 dollars of police service.
So, Mayor, for the council,
I think boys before you,
who is a more professional services,
in person who has been incurred.
From January 1st, 2020,
forth from January 3rd,
we're very, very important at the city of May 1st.
This is boys focused on completing
five months in the documentation,
additional communication between the attorneys in the city.
Regarding the game,
safety issues,
the rights to the city,
and the committee,
and the Senate,
the transport study,
the amount of amendment in the
the sort of court appeals to follow up.
About the second or fifth thousand in the
budget for this month,
we here in the area related,
we're related in the rights of the clients,
the civil litigation,
the balance of that,
to the fifth thousand term,
we have 500,
we have 24,000,
we're going to complete the other set of steps in.
If you do approve the claim,
or 24,000,
you're going to be making the other places.
That would leave us on the main balance.
This is the school year,
499,000,
five hundred and five hundred,
three five dollars,
five hundred and five cents.
Yeah,
there's been a lot of new,
the remainder came out of the law
in the discussion.
As well as some great discussion
between our students,
the need of the authority to learn.
And much more important.
Same.
Same five.
The Williams.
Double five.
Same.
And, try to take me in your announcements.
I'll let you in for a minute.
No.
All right.